Narrator: 1
A: The busiest street in the country is Madero Avenue, in Mexico City.
Up to 500,000 people a day walk along this street in the capital of Mexico.
Narrator: 2
B: The biggest train station in the world is Grand Central Terminal in New York.
It has 44 platforms and covers nearly 2 million square feet.
Narrator: 3
A: The widest bridge in the country is the Port Mann Bridge, near Vancouver.
This Canadian bridge is 213 feet wide – wide enough for ten lanes of traffic.
Narrator: 4
B: The tallest building in the world is Burj Khalifa in the United Arab Emirates.
It is 2,716.5 feet tall.
Narrator: 5
A: The longest river in the world is the Nile.
It’s 4,258 miles long and goes through eleven different African countries.
Narrator: 6
B: The most dangerous road in the world is Bayburt D915 in Türkiye.
The 65-mile road is very high up and the weather is often foggy and rainy.
Even really good drivers find driving extremely difficult.